(Amy:)We postulate an alternate
world that differs from ours
(Amy:)in one key aspect and then
pose questions to each other.
It's fun for ages eight to 80.
(Sheldon:)Join us.
(Sheldon:)All right.
(Leonard:)I like a good brainteaser.
(Leonard:)Give it a whirl.
You're in luck;
this is an easy one.
(Sheldon:)In a world where mankind is ruled
(Sheldon:)by a giant intelligent beaver,
(Sheldon:)what food is no longer consumed?
(Leonard:)Uh... a BLT where the
"B" stands for beaver?
(Leonard:)I don't know.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, be serious.
(Sheldon:)We're playing a game here.
(clears throat)
(Leonard:)I can figure this out.
(Leonard:)Let's see.
(Leonard:)Um, well, beavers eat tree bark.
(Leonard:)The only tree bark I know that
humans consume is cinnamon.
(Leonard:)So, I'll say cinnamon.
(Sheldon:)Incorrect.
(Sheldon:)Obviously, the answer
is cheese Danish.
(Leonard:)What?
(Amy:)In a world ruled by a giant beaver,
(Amy:)mankind builds many dams to
please the beaver overlord.
(Amy:)The low-lying city of
Copenhagen is flooded.
(Amy:)Thousands die.
(Amy:)Devastated, the Danes never
invent their namesake pastry.